



Summary

With 16 years of experience in fashion retail, I've handled front and back-office roles and diverse responsibilities. Additionally, I owned and operated an online store before transitioning to the tech industry through an immersive bootcamp course at <Academia de Código_>.

Pursuing a degree in International Trade was also a significant achievement.

Now, I'm eager to bring my problem-solving abilities, passion for learning, and expertise in online retail to the constantly evolving tech landscape.

Experience

Founder | Birds Bloq Jan 2022 - Mar 2023

Business Development & Expansion Specialist | Salsa Jeans Oct 2019 - Aug 2022

Stock Controller | Salsa Jeans May 2014 - Sep 2019

Store Manager | Salsa Jeans Mar 2008 - Apr 2014

Sales Assistant | Salsa Jeans Nov 2005 - Feb 2008

Hobbies

Literature, music, drums, tennis, gym.

Education

<Academia de Código_>

A 14-Week Intensive & Description of the Amp; Amp; Immersive Full Stack Programming Bootcamp Jan 2023 - Apr 2023

Instituto Superior de Contabilidade e Administração do Porto

Licentiate degree, International Trade 2017 - 2020

Instituto Superior de Engenharia do Porto Electronics Engineering 2003 - 2004

Skills

Languages: Java, JavaScript, CSS, HTML, SQL

Frameworks & Others

- Maven
- Tomcat
- ES6
- REST
- JDBC && JPA
- JUnit
- Git

- jQuery
- Bootstrap
- Spring Framework
- Spring MVC
- Scrum && Kanban
- MySQL
- Agile Methodologies

Languages

English, Spanish and Portuguese.



LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/adrianoluissousa



Address

Guimarães, Portugal





Email adrianoluissousa@gmail.com



GitHub<a>NeonDada